# William Gledhill

williamswgledhill@gmail.com

0435 397 746

3180 Barton Highway, Murrumbateman, NSW

Dear the Vintner's Daughter team,

Hello! I have been somewhat familiar with your vineyard for a while, as my father, Scott Gledhill, owns and runs Wimbaliri Wines. I see your green and cream shed from the top of the hill every day, I remember it specifically over all the other sheds because I once visited when I was very little.

I have grown up here since 2010 (I am 18), and am familiar with most of the jobs that occur in the operations of a vineyard. I think the only job I haven't done at some point is spraying.

I am attending university full time so I can't work standard 8 hour days, but I have a decent amount of spare time (at the moment on Monday, Tuesday and Wednesday) and am totally free on the weekend. I have a long holiday coming up and can change my classes next term to have entirely free days.

I would prefer to do the vineyard job as I like being outside but am fully qualified to do the sales job, although I have not done sales before.

I also have a job at Eden Road Wines although work is sporadic. My minimum rate for any work is the award rate I get there (about \$29/hour).

Yours sincerely, William Gledhill

# **Experience**

- Work experience program at the Australian Signals Directorate (June 2023)
- Working casually as a vineyard hand at Eden Road Wines (Dec 2022 - present)
- Running several ecommerce websites (Jan 2024 - present)

## Qualifications

- RSA
- Drivers licence
- Year 12 Certificate
- Tocal College pruning course

## **Education**

- Educated at Daramalan College (2018 - 2023)
- Student at ANU studying
  Business & Computing (Feb 2024 - present)

## **Technical Skills**

- HTML & CSS
- Bootstrap Framework
- PHP & SQL
- JS & C++ (familiarity)
- Shopify
- TikTok & Meta ad managers
- Video editing (capcut)
- Graphic design (Canva)

- Copywriting
- 3D modelling
- Pruning & picking
- Operating some machinery

### **Interests & hobbies**

- Biographies of historical figures
- History of Australia
- History of England
- Biking around Canberra

#### **Awards**

- Academic Excellence (Yr 11 & Yr 12)
- Subject Award (Design & graphics)